NIRMAL SHAH

Somerville,MA| 781-475-3226 | shahhr1cky@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/nirmal-ricky-shah | www.nirmal-shah.com |

SUMMARY

I am a Full-stack developer who aims to create work that embodies uniqueness, creativity and clarity. I am a passionate human who works hard to offer creative solutions to help others in any way I can. My technical experience with Html, Css, Javascript, Node.js, React and PHP allow me to bring these creative solutions to life in digital spaces.

SKILLS & LANGUAGES

•	HTML	•	Javascript	•	Php
•	1 1 1 1 1 1 1	•	Javaschibi	•	טוו ו

- CSS ReactJS Express.js
- GithubNode.jsPostgreSql
- Python

PROJECTS

The Guitar World

- Technology used Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Ejs.
- Online website to purchase awesome guitars.

Restaurants On The Go

- Technology used React.js, Github, Express.js, MongoDB, Zomato Api.
- An app to find top 10 restaurants from the cities around the world.

Health-Diary

- Technology used PostgreSql, React.js, PHP.
- App to track health related events.

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineering Fellow, General Assembly

Aug 2020 - Nov 2020

- Developed competitive full stack web development skills with special emphasis on new technology and processes through a full-time immersive course.
- Worked independently and in small teams to deploy projects within strict deadlines.

Guest service Aide + Front Desk Agent(Trainee) , Marriott Int

Apr 2019 - Mar 2020

- As a trainee, made keys for the guests using the Marriott PMS system.
- Helped the guests with the navigation around the hotel property and the city.

Cashier, Dunkin' Donut, Medford, MA

Jan 2019 - Dec 2019

- Handled a busy store with the orders, register and a very busy drive thru.
- Assisted manager with inventory and overall store operations.

Store-keeper, Hlmalayan Brewery LTD, Lalitpur, Nepal

Feb 2014 - Nov 2018

- Prepared Monthly and yearly reports of the inventory for computation of balance sheet.
- Maintained records of incoming and outgoing inventories.
- Follow up with the procurement for purchase of raw materials, packaging materials and machinery items.

EDUCATION

- General Assembly, Software Engineering Certificate Remote
- United Academy, Faculty (Science) Nepal